egypttoursportal.com 2019-08-26

# Privacy Policy of Egypt Tours Portal

Our company “ **Egypt Tours Portal** ” was created on the principle of providing the finest touring experience for our entire clients. All our tour packages are customized according to every traveler’s individual budget and interests while maintaining the highest standards of quality service, security, and professionalism, all for the purpose of creating the memories of a lifetime around the heart and the corners of this magical country.

We are totally honored by your choice and we appreciate & value your total trust in us to create your dream vacation. Our main goal is to establish a trust system with all of our clients which will encourage them to return to Egypt for various times once again. One of the principles that distinguish us is our commitment to operate all of our tours in total honesty and reliability from the initial moment of the booking until the completion of the tour and beyond. Your security and the safety of your data are also our main priority as all your personal information or any kind of information provided from you to us will be kept in complete privacy and confidentiality.

It would be great if you read all of our privacy practices and keep in mind that by using our website and resources you are accepting our privacy policies.

## The Collected Information from You

  1. All the Credit/Debit cards details and personally identifiable information won’t be stored, sold, shared, rented, or leased to any other party of any kind.
  2. Our website policies terms & conditions could be altered or updated occasionally to meet the required standards. So we recommend all of our clients to visit these sections in order to be updated of all the changes of the website as modifications will be effective on the day they are posted.

## How Your Information is Protected?

You will get the sensation of confidence and safety while using our website & travel arrangements as all of your transactions and information are protected at the highest level. We use the best implementations in the market to guard and secure all of your important & sensitive information through administrative, electronic and physical security measures. Our website utilizes firewalls & intrusion detection systems to stop any hack or breakdown in our system or the access to your information by any unauthorized persons. Only the employees who are handling your account will have access to your personal information and only at the time when they are handling a business transaction. All of your personal information is encrypted while being transmitted through our system or to other needed users of that information.

## External Links

If you linked our website to another, remember that these sites don’t operate under our privacy policy so we advise that you read all of their privacy statements to fully understand their procedures for collection, using and disclosing personal information.
